... more  No address associated with this project Closed N/A On Track Due Today Due in %1$dd Overdue Google Maps is currently disabled Google Maps is not installed on this device Search Loading… Clear Reset Title OK Marking official response... Unmarking official response... No items Offline mode Device incompatible with pdf viewer None of your apps can open this file. Please check out the Play Store. %1$d of %2$d The Download Manager is disabled. Please enable it in settings. The download will start when online Download Error Open Settings Cancel Failed to share the photo. Please try again. Send To No email applications found. Download Complete Download failed. Please try again. Delete Deleted Are you sure you would like to delete this item? Search %1$s… Open Allow Procore to Use Camera? Camera access is required to take photos. Storage permissions are required to download files. Failed to share the data. Please try again. Print Failed to print. Please try again. Video streaming is only available online Add Photos Select a Status \* Required No Projects You are not a member of any company projects Status Change Status None … more  %1$d RFI %1$d RFIs   %1$d Submittal %1$d Submittals   %1$d T&M Ticket %1$d T&M Tickets  Device does not support viewing 360 photos  %1$d Prime Contract %1$d Prime Contracts  Press back button again to exit Description You are currently offline You must have a network connection to download attachments. Reconnect to your network and try again. Download Attachments There are more than %1$d items to download. This may take a while depending on your network. Consider filtering the number of items down further. Large download Download Last checked less than a minute ago Last checked %1$s @string/hour Download completed  %1$d item %1$d items  Cannot download attachments No new items available Download all attachments Downloading... Downloaded %1$d of %2$d Feedback Add feedback… Send Owner/Client: Contract Dates Date Created Start Date Estimated Completion Date Substantial Completion Date Actual Completion Date Contract Date Signed Contract Received Date Execution Date Issued On Date Returned Date Letter of Intent Date Approval Letter Date Contract Termination Date Prime Contract Information Contractor Architect/Engineer Executed Default Retainage Created By Private Contract Summary Report Remaining Balance Outstanding Percent Paid Payments Received Owner Invoices Draft Change Orders Pending Revised Contract Pending Change Orders Approved Change Orders Original Contract Revised Contract \# %1$s Yes No  Attachment: \(%1$s\) Attachments: \(%1$s\)  %1$s%% %1$s: %2$s Show Less Show More Terminated Out for Signature Out for Bid Complete Approved Draft Provide Feedback Unknown Calendar View Filters hour min Go to settings

